<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivan Noden</title>
    <link>http://ivannoden.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ivan Noden</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ivannoden.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes on Elliptic Curves with Complex Multiplication</title>
      <link>http://ivannoden.com/posts/elliptic_curves_with_cm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://ivannoden.com/posts/elliptic_curves_with_cm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the summer of 2024, I was funded by UCL to undertake a research project
under the supervision of Assoc. Prof. Cecilia Busuioc. I am very grateful to
UCL for funding this and especially thankful for all the work Cecilia did in
helping me with the project. She was a brilliant supervisor and I am very glad
to have been able to work with her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was on elliptic curves with complex multiplication. Below is
attached a set of explanatory notes on the topic and I have pasted the
introduction here for convenience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMA TMT 2024 Conference: Patterns in Prime Numbers</title>
      <link>http://ivannoden.com/posts/tmt_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://ivannoden.com/posts/tmt_talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The slides for a group presentation on the top &lt;strong&gt;Patterns in Prime Numbers&lt;/strong&gt;
centering around a discussion of Bunyakovsky&amp;rsquo;s Conjecture, in which we touch on
Dirichlet&amp;rsquo;s Theorem, Schinzel&amp;rsquo;s Conjecture, the Twin Prime Conjecture and more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last summer, I, Bruno Eaves, and Ioannis Pantelidakis gave a presentation on
&lt;strong&gt;Patterns in Prime Numbers&lt;/strong&gt;, focusing on a discussion around Bunyakovsky&amp;rsquo;s
conjecture which captures many open questions related to prime numbers. This
March, we were very grateful to have the opportunity to give this presentation
at the IMA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s Mathematicians Today 2024&amp;rsquo; undergraduate conference.
It was a wonderful event with many great talks so I would very much like to
thank the IMA, the University of Greenwich, Tony Mann, and all others involved
in organising the conference which you can read more about
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/view/imatmt2024/home&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I would also like to
congratulate Andi Hani and Mingjia Yan for winning the prize for best
presentation and the popular vote prize respectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
